11main.com 2015-03-18

# 11 Main Privacy Policy

At 11 Main, we value our community. You trust us with your information, and we're serious about that responsibility. We believe in transparency, and we're committed to being upfront about our privacy practices, including how we treat personal information we collect or receive. We know you care about your privacy, too, so we provide settings that allow you to control how certain information is used on 11 Main. This policy explains our privacy practices.

* ### Security

Your security is important to us. Your 11 Main account information is protected by a password. It is important that you protect against unauthorized access of your account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and computer secure by signing out after using our services. 11 Main encrypts sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 11 Main follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once 11 Main receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is absolutely secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 11 Main offers optional advanced security settings for members, such as two-factor authentication for signing in, full-site SSL, and login history; you can enable these options under your account settings.

* ### Information Collected or Received

#### 1\. Required Information

As an 11 Main member, you are required to provide a valid email address at registration. Depending on which services you choose to use, 11 Main may require information such as 

  * a shop name,
  * billing and payment information (including billing address, credit card information),
  * a telephone number, and
  * a physical mailing address.

If you choose to enable direct checkout, 11 Main may require information for proof of identity.

11 Main may contact individual shop owners to confidentially request more information about their shops or items listed on the site to ensure compliance with our rules.

#### 2\. Visible Information

Other people may see your:

  * shop name,
  * date joined,
  * profile information, including items, shops and categories you mark as interesting to you,
  * items listed for sale,
  * shop pages,
  * sold item listings, and
  * comments in community spaces.

#### 3\. Browser Information

11 Main automatically receives and records some information from your browser when you visit the site, such as your: 

  * IP address,
  * cookies and
  * data about which pages you visit on the site through the use of log files provided by our third-party tracking-utility partners.

This information helps us analyze and understand how the site works for members and visitors, and provide a more personalized experience for members and visitors. 11 Main uses a variety of technologies to help us better understand how people use our site and services.

#### 4\. Third Party Information

Some members or visitors may connect to, or register an 11 Main account using an external third-party application, such as Facebook, or an app developed using 11 Main APIs. 11 Main may receive some data from those connected third-party applications. Connecting your 11 Main account to third-party applications or services is optional, and when you connect your account to an external app, you will be given the opportunity to grant permission.

If you have optionally connected your account to an unaffiliated, third-party application, such as Facebook or an app developed using 11 Main APIs, you can remove permission for the app by changing your 11 Main account settings or changing the account settings of the third party application to which you connected your 11 Main account.

We may receive, or collect supplemental information about you from third parties sources and add it to our account information. This may include, but is not limited to, demographic, navigation information, additional contact information, credit check information, and additional information about you from credit bureaus or other sources, as permitted by law.

#### 5\. Non-Members

11 Main may receive or collect information (for example: email address) about a person who is not yet a registered 11 Main member (a " **non-member** ") in connection with certain 11 Main features, including but not limited to:

  * a non-member subscribing to an 11 Main newsletter,
  * a member inviting a non-member to visit 11 Main.com,
  * a non-member engaging in a transaction, or
  * a member sending a coupon or gift card code to a non-member.

Non-member information is used only for the purpose for which it was originally submitted to 11 Main. Non-members can contact 11 Main Support if they do not want 11 Main to retain their information.

#### 6\. Minors

11 Main's Terms of Use require all account owners to be at least 18 years of age (or have the permission and supervision of a responsible parent or legal guardian).

* ### Mobile Use

When you download or use our Mobile Applications, or access one of our mobile optimized sites, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. We may use this information to provide you with location based services, such as advertising, search results and other personalized content. Most mobile devices allow you to control or disable location services in the device's settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device's location services, we recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or the manufacture of your particular device.

* ### Cookies and similar technologies

11 Main uses a variety of technologies to help us better understand how people use our site and services. You may manage or disable cookies and similar technologies in your browser settings and thus our ability to track some, or all of this data, depending upon your browser and your device. However, if you block cookies or our ability to, or the ability of others to gather your information, you may not be able to take advantage of certain site features, services, applications or tools. For more information on how you can block, delete, or disable cookies and similar technologies, please review your browser and device settings.  11 Main does not respond to “Do Not Track” (DNT) signals or mechanisms.

This site also uses Inspectlet web analytics service. For a small proportion of users, Inspectlet may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, and scrolling activity. Inspectlet does not collect any personally identifiable information, nor does it track your browsing habits across web sites. We are using the information collected by Inspectlet to improve our website, make it more user-friendly and monitor that it is performing correctly.

* ### User Control

We know members of our community value having control over their own information. 11 Main gives you the choice of providing, editing or removing certain information, as well as choice over how we contact you.

#### 1\. Account Data

You may change or correct your 11 Main account information (except your username). You may remove certain optional information you no longer wish to be publicly visible, such as your full name.

#### 2\. Messages from 11 Main

On occasion, 11 Main will contact you. Primarily, messages are delivered by email, and every account is required to keep a valid email address on file to receive messages. In some situations, 11 Main may contact you by telephone, chat, SMS message, mobile application, or physical mail in order to provide you with information about products and features you may find of interest, or to provide you with customer support. You may update your contact preferences in your account settings.

  1. **Required Messages**

Some messages from 11 Main are service-related and required for members. Examples of service-related messages include, but are not limited to: a welcome/confirmation email when you register your account, notification of an order and order status, or correspondence with 11 Main's support team. These messages are not promotional in nature. You may not opt out of receiving service-related messages from 11 Main, unless you close your account.

  2. **Product Messages**

As a member, 11 Main may also send you messages related to certain features on the site or your activity. 11 Main may also send you news or updates about changes to our site or services. By default, members will receive these messages via email, but you may choose to opt out of getting certain emails under your account settings.

  3. **Newsletters**

11 Main offers optional email newsletters. When you register for an account or choose to subscribe, you will receive newsletters from us. Newsletters are available to both members and non-members. Members may subscribe or unsubscribe from optional newsletters under their account settings, or by following the instructions contained in the newsletter emails. Non-members may subscribe by providing an email address, which will only be used by 11 Main for these newsletters. Non-members may unsubscribe from newsletters by following the instructions contained in the newsletter emails.

* ### Disclosure

11 Main will not intentionally sell or disclose your name, email address or other personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this policy.

#### 1\. Transactions

As part of the buying and selling process, 11 Main will share information between the two members involved in the transaction. You may obtain another 11 Main member's email address, shipping address, payment information, and/or other information. As described in 11 Main's Terms of Use, you have a limited license to use this information only for 11 Main-related communications or for 11 Main-facilitated transactions. 11 Main has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without express consent from that person, you must not add any 11 Main member to your email or physical mailing list.

#### 2\. Legally Required Disclosure

11 Main may release your personal information to a third party in order comply with a subpoena or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of 11 Main's Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with our Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, 11 Main may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company name.

#### 3\. Affiliates

11 Main is affiliated with a variety of businesses and works closely with them. These businesses may offer promotions or sell items or services to you through 11 Main's services. 11 Main may also provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. Due to the nature of our business model, when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, we may share information that is related to such transaction with that affiliated business. 11 Main may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

#### 4\. Third Parties Generally

We can only speak for ourselves; this policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that 11 Main does not own or control, or individuals that 11 Main does not employ or manage. If you provide your information to others on 11 Main or throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the information you provide to them. 11 Main does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. 11 Main is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the 11 Main site. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

  1. **Third-Party Service Providers**

11 Main employs other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf, and we need to share your personally identifiable information with them to provide products and services to you. Examples include but are not limited to fulfilling orders, processing payments, handling billing disputes and collections, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, fraud prevention, identity verification and providing customer service. 11 Main may partner with third-party services for fraud prevention and/or identity verification. 11 Main also may partner with third-party services that may use various tracking technologies, such as browser cookies, Web beacons, or Flash cookies, to provide certain services or features, and to collect information, such as your device identifier, IP address or identifier for advertising (IDFA). These technologies allow a partner to recognize your computer each time you visit 11 Main, but do not allow access to personally identifiable information that you have provided to 11 Main. 11 Main does not have access or control over these third-party technologies, and they are not covered by our privacy statement.

For more information on third-party advertising related cookies and how to opt out of them, please visit the following website: http://www.aboutads.info/choices.

  2. **Third-Party Content**

When you load a page on the 11 Main site that incorporates certain third-party content, the website that is the source of the content site may request cookies directly from your browser. For example, when you a load a page on 11 Main that has a social plug-in from a third-party site or service, such as a "Like" or "Send" button, you are also loading content from that third-party site. 11 Main does not prevent third-party sites from collecting your personally identifiable information in these circumstances. These interactions and any collection of  data by these third-party sites are subject to the privacy policy of the third-party site.

  3. **Merchant Referrals**

If you register with 11 Main through a merchant referral, we may contact you with product announcements, news and other offers; we may also provide your email to the referring merchant.

#### 5\. Acquisitions

In some cases, 11 Main may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, member information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. 11 Main will transfer information about you if 11 Main is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 11 Main will notify you by email or by putting a notice on the site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

* ### Data Retention

11 Main will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you no longer want 11 Main to use your information to provide you services, you may close your account. 11 Main will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

* ### Privacy Policy Changes

11 Main reserves the right to modify this privacy statement as well as its Terms of Use and other Subpolicies at any time, as described in the Terms of Use.

* ### Notice To California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. Under Section 1798.83, 11 Main does not share any of your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent, except as specified in this policy.

* ### Contact 11 Main

If you have questions or suggestions, you can contact 11 Main's support team via our Help Center.
